My parents would be like, "DERRICK, WE'D
LIKE Y'ALL we'd like for you to get a
girlfriend." And I'd have to tell my
mom, "Y'all just bought me overalls. I
drive dad's truck. You make my lunches.
There's a rumor at school that I've got
a family, mom."
>> [laughter]
>> I'm from Alabama. I I now live in
Colorado. I've lived in Denver for 5
years, so I tell people I have time
traveled, which is nice. I went from
cleaning out horse stalls to actually
plugging in vehicles, so it's been quite
the adjustment.
>> [laughter]
>> It's been quite the adjustment, you
know.
I think we should talk about the
obvious, you know, what's going on. And
that's masks. I think masks are great. I
think people should wear them in social
settings. I think they make a
difference. I want people to know that I
haven't heard anything that anybody has
said in a year.
I've never given up on so many
conversations in my entire life.
I mean, people will be in THE MIDDLE OF
TALKING. I'm like, "YOU KNOW WHAT,
JESSICA? JUST SHOOT ME AN EMAIL."
>> [laughter]
>> IT SOUNDS LIKE YOU'RE DROWNING right
now. And the closer I get to you, the
further you back away, and it's weird in
the office. I got to tell you.
>> [laughter]
>> And y'all know just as well as I do, if
you go ahead and pull down your mask,
that is the same as pointing a gun at
the ceiling.
I mean, PEOPLE WILL BOUNCE THEIR HEAD
OFF THE FLOOR. I mean, they go SPRINTING
DOWN THE HALLWAY. "HE'S GOT THE VIRUS!"
[screaming]
>> [laughter]
>> I JUST WANT Y'ALL TO HEAR ME.
>> IT'S A TOUGH TIME, MAN.
AND I KNOW I'M GOING TO KEEP THE MASK
ON. I WANT TO WEAR IT. I JUST I CAN'T
BREATHE WITHOUT THE MASK. Y'ALL I mean,
y'all see me. I'm not jogging out here.
I mean, I'm trying to tie my SHOES WITH
THE MASK ON. I LOOK LIKE A DOLPHIN
coming up for air every
I'm trying I mean, it's SeaWorld in
here. I'm trying to JUST TO TIE MY
SHOES.
>> [laughter]
>> I DON'T KNOW.
I DON'T HAVE ANY NUMBERS to back it up,
but I do feel like my uglier friends
wear their masks more.
>> [laughter]
>> I do. I I don't have any science with
that, but I do have some buddies. I
mean, trying to talk to some women
They've got the They've got their masks
to their hairline. Trying to talk to
women They've got Listen, I own a Volvo.
Give me a minute here. YOU
>> [laughter]
>> BE A WEIRD TIME TO TRY TO COURT SOMEBODY
right now, you know?
Both of you have masks on. It's really
HARD. THAT'S A TOUGH WAY I MEAN, YOU'RE
out to eat, you know, maybe somewhere
nice like Cracker Barrel. Things are
going smooth.
>> [laughter]
>> Y'all laugh ABOUT CRAP. I'M TALKING
ABOUT LITTLE CRACKER BARREL. THINGS GO
AND THEN WE HIT THE GIFT SHOP, you know?
You don't know who Ricky Skaggs is, get
a cassette. We're having A GOOD TIME.
>> [laughter]
>> BUT YEAH, YOU GOT TO SAY YOU KNOW, THE
BISCUITS come out and you got to say
something weird before you get into
them, you know, like hey Ashley, will
you show me your teeth, you know?
Which is a weird thing to do, BUT WE'RE
ABOUT TO BITE into these biscuits and I
want to see what she's chewing with, you
know?
Just go We'll check them like came out.
We'll just lift up one side. We'll lift
up the other. Looks pretty healthy,
Ashley.
>> [laughter]
>> I don't know. It's a big deal to me. I'm
a flosser. I want to know that you
floss, too, you know? I've earned my
flossing. Flossing's not just something
you can just do on a Tuesday afternoon.
We've earned our flossing. My gums don't
bleed anymore. It took me years to GET
HERE. IT FEELS GOOD TO FLOSS.
Y'ALL DON'T SOME OF Y'ALL GET IT. SOME
OF Y'ALL LIKE MY MY GUMS MY GUMS YOU
KNOW WHY? CUZ YOU'RE NOT FLOSSING, ALL
RIGHT?
AND YEAH, 2020 WAS A BIG YEAR,
NON-FLOSSERS. Y'ALL JUST WALKING AROUND
WITH WHOLE CHICKEN LEGS HANGING OUT OF
YOUR FRONT TEETH. NOBODY KNEW IT. NOBODY
KNEW IT, DID THEY?
WELL, OH YEAH, DON'T YOU CLAP.
DON'T YOU
AND SOME OF Y'ALL SOMETIMES WHEN I SAY
THAT, PEOPLE ACT LIKE IT'S SHALLOW. I'm
like, do you pick your partners by their
eyeballs? Is that what you do? You see
somebody blinking, you're like, we're
starting a family. I can tell.
I've seen a lot OF PEOPLE BLINK, BUT
SHE'S REALLY got a blink about her. I
mean, she does.
>> [laughter]
>> I don't know. People have come up with
really unique ways to make you feel less
than with these masks, you know?
Living in downtown Denver, I've got a
I'll have my mask on, you know, the
other person will have their mask on and
we're both headed down the sidewalk
towards each other and right before we
get to each other, they cross the
street.
I don't know if y'all can tell yet, but
I'm pretty fiery. I cross the street
with them.
>> [laughter]
>> I've got a few questions and the first
one is WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
I'VE GOT A BETTER MASK ON THAN YOU DO
AND A BUNCH OF GEL IN MY HAIR. We're
going TO PLAY THE ODDS TODAY.
>> [laughter]
>> I DON'T KNOW.
IT'S JUST MY THOUGHTS.
Covid's made it weird, you know. I'm an
Android guy. I don't know if there's any
Android users. Tough life for an Android
user during Covid. I haven't seen a menu
in over a year.
>> [laughter]
>> Some of y'all don't get this. I'VE GOT
50 PICTURES OF BARCODES. That's it.
That's all I've got.
>> [laughter]
>> I MEAN, IF NOBODY AROUND ME HAS AN
IPHONE, we're going chicken fingers.
That's the only option. 90% of the
places serve it, it's not weird. I can
just order that.
>> [laughter]
>> I don't know.
It's easy to be observational when
you're from somewhere like Alabama and
you move out west.
Everything kind of shows up to me, you
know? Like, I own a bunch of popular
clothes on accident. There's this big
hipster movement going on that's going
full circle right back to me that I
never saw coming.
>> [laughter]
>> And some of y'all will understand this.
If you go to any coffee shop in any
decent size city, the person serving you
that latte these days is going to be
wearing a a whole lot of Carhartt.
When I was growing up, Carhartt meant
that you were real country, you know?
Your dad might be a plumber. Y'all were
rented deer meat, you know?
Math wasn't something you got excited
about. Carhartt was different in the
'90s.
Now, everybody's got it on and it's
mind-blowing. I got it for every
Christmas. I mean, my whole life and my
dad would say the same thing every time.
That right there is going to LAST YOU
FOREVER.
>> [laughter]
>> AND THAT'S COOL. IT'S NICE TO HAVE
CLOTHES THAT LAST. A
FAMOUS BECAUSE IT doesn't shrink when
you wash it wash it. It doesn't hang on
fences.
BUT I MEAN, WHEN YOU'RE 14, YOU DON'T
WANT COVERALLS. I WOULD MY MY PARENTS
WOULD BE LIKE, "DEREK, WE'D LIKE Y'ALL
YOU'D LIKE FOR YOU to get a girlfriend."
And I'd have to tell my mom, "Y'all just
bought me overalls. I drive dad's truck.
You make my lunches. There's a rumor at
school that I've got a family, Mom."
>> [laughter]
>> I LOOK LIKE A WORKING MAN. I DO.
EVERYBODY THINKS I'M PUNCHING IN AND
OUT, YOU KNOW?
>> [laughter]
>> IT WASN'T COOL TO LOOK LIKE A COAL MINER
IN '96. I hate to break IT TO PEOPLE.
NOW, IF YOU'VE GOT RIPPED JEANS AND A
CARHARTT SWEATSHIRT, YOU'RE A COOL GUY.
LET ME TELL YOU SOMETHING. IN ALABAMA,
IF YOU'VE GOT RIPPED JEANS and a
Carhartt sweatshirt, you have A GRAVEL
DRIVEWAY.
>> [laughter]
>> JUST THE WAY IT IS.
>> SAME THING WITH THE brand Champion.
I know all y'all In the '90s, you wanted
any brand besides the brand Champion.
Now, it's super popular. Champion was a
Kmart brand.
It was the only brand that would come
brand new with the tags on it and still
smell like cigarettes.
>> [laughter]
>> I CAN REMEMBER. I'M LIKE, "I DON'T KNOW
HOW THIS SMELLS LIKE AUNT SHEILA, MOM. I
don't under But it's IN THE PACKAGE."
>> [laughter]
>> THERE WAS NOTHING COOL ABOUT CHAMPION.
>> I MEAN, ONE OF MY BUDDIES, DAKOTA, he
was like, "Derek, calm down, man. You're
freaking out. Champion just made a
comeback."
I said, "Dakota, I'm going to tell you
what a comeback is, my man.
That means you were once here.
AND NOW YOU'RE BACK AGAIN. CHAMPION JUST
GOT HERE!
IT WOULD BE LIKE IF NEXT WEEK, FADED
GLORY WAS ALL OVER INSTAGRAM! [laughter]
RAGS TO RICHES. THIS IS THE TRUE
AMERICAN STORY.
THIS ISN'T A COMEBACK. THIS IS A COME
UP, MY MAN!
>> [laughter]
>> DID Y'ALL EVER THINK I'M 36 years old?
Did y'all ever think that you would see
that flooding your pants would be
popular? Did y'all ever see that one? I
can tell you 10 years ago if you showed
up to a high school and your pants
weren't touching your shoes, nobody was
talking TO YOU.
>> [laughter]
>> NOW SHOWING A LITTLE ANKLE IS THE MAN,
YOU ARE THE MAN. LET LET YOUR JEANS STOP
ABOUT SHIN SHIN RIGHT THERE. THAT LOOKS
GOOD. LET'S GET SOME COOL SOCKS. LOOK AT
WHEN I GOT SOCKS FOR CHRISTMAS GROWING
UP, I KNEW MY GRADES NEEDED TO come up
JUST A TAD.
>> [laughter]
>> AND YOU KNOW WHAT SHORT JEANS ARE
CALLED?
CAPRIS!
THEY'RE CALLED CAPRIS!
START CALLING THEM I DON'T CARE, JASON,
IF YOU'VE GOT ON SHORT JEANS, BUT YOU,
MY MAN, HAVE ON CAPRIS!
>> [laughter]
>> I MEAN, ALL THESE THINGS I GOT MADE FUN
OF FOR GROWING UP ARE NOW POPULAR.
Did you know that growing your own
plants, watering your own vegetables is
NOW A HOBBY?
>> [laughter]
>> I'M TELLING Y'ALL, YOU GET TWO FERNS,
THREE CACTUSES, GET ON INSTAGRAM, LOOK
AT THE FOLLOWERS.
>> [laughter]
>> THAT HURTS MY FEELINGS.
IN ALABAMA, I GREW UP WITH A 10-ACRE
GARDEN, AND EVERYBODY I WOULD TELL ABOUT
it would donate TO MY FAMILY.
>> [laughter]
>> THERE WAS NOTHING COOL ABOUT GROWING
YOUR OWN TO- I NEVER SAW MY MOM SNAPPING
BEANS LIKE, "OH, WHAT A BLESSING THAT IT
TAKES US AN HOUR TO GET TO KROGER. THIS
IS INCREDIBLE.
WE SHOULD MAKE OUR OWN JAM AGAIN, BILL.
I LOVE THIS LIFE."
>> [laughter]
>> NOW IT'S COOL.
THAT'S CRAZY TO ME.
>> [laughter]
>> THERE'S ALL these things that are
popular that
they stick out to me, you know?
Rescuing dogs.
I think rescuing dogs is a great thing.
I want y'all to know that I've rescued a
dog.
But I want y'all to know that if you
live out in the country,
we've been rescuing dogs for a long
time.
Okay? If If you live out in the country,
if a dog comes in your yard without a
collar on and he stands there for too
long,
that's your dog now.
Yeah.
You know what? It's not a ticket to
heaven or a Facebook status. That's a
third mixed lab.
>> [laughter]
>> MHM.
AND I TELL PEOPLE OUT IN THE COUNTRY, WE
WORK for our strays way more than city
folk do.
DOWNTOWN, THEY GO TO SOME SHELTER and
they hand them this mixed lab that's a
Sagittarius just like they are, you
know? Both of you like macaroni and
cheese. You're going to live a long life
together.
>> [laughter]
>> OUT IN THE COUNTRY, WE'RE OUT IN AN OPEN
FIELD. LIKE, IF YOU WANT A GOOD HOME,
YOU'RE GOING TO QUIT RUNNING. SOMEBODY
TACKLE THAT WINNER DOG!
>> [laughter]
>> I MEAN, WE'RE IN MINIVANS GOING DOWN THE
STREET JUST TRYING TO WHISTLE, THROWING
OUT CHEESE PUFFS. WE WILL LOVE YOU! GET
IN THE VAN!
>> [laughter]
>> WE EARN OURS, YOU KNOW?
IT'S DIFFERENT.
Y'all having fun?
>> YEAH!
>> [applause]
>> SORRY, I'M ABOUT TO PASS OUT UP HERE. I
HAD
I DON'T KNOW, you know, a lot of things.
I'd never seen anybody pick up dog poop
until I moved to Colorado.
I'd never seen it once.
>> [laughter]
>> Did y'all know they don't do it in
movies? Did y'all know that? You got to
watch it live. It's like music, you
know? It's like, if you want it good,
you got to go to the park.
Y'all can call me old school, call me
what you want, but I'm from a place
where we just run over it with a lawn
mower until we can't find it anymore.
Y'all know what I mean? You kind of
circle back around on it and you look at
it and you're like, you know what? I
think I've diced it UP PRETTY GOOD.
>> [applause]
>> AND YOU KNOW ALWAYS TELL HOW BIG IT IS.
Y'ALL KNOW THE I MEAN YOU'LL HIT IT, YOU
KNOW, and you'll kind of get that little
bounce like that. It's like that. And
then you'll get a whiff of it and you'll
I got to circle back on that one.
We're We're going to have [laughter] to
hit it one more time. That's a bad one
right there.
Then you go, "HEY, DID YOU FEED HIM
TWICE?
I MEAN IT'S LIKE A SPEED BUMP OUT HERE.
>> [laughter]
>> MY GOODNESS, I ALMOST LOST A TIRE.
I JUST NEVER THOUGHT I'D SEE PEOPLE
BENDING OVER STANDING BEHIND a golden
retriever that's taking a bigger poop
than they've taken yet. Just I mean if
you're a good neighbor you'll catch it
before it hits the ground, you know? I
mean y'all don't let it hit the grass.
I'M A GOOD NEIGHBOR. I'M A GOOD
NEIGHBOR. You know I am.
Walking around swinging it in your hand
talking about I might go to TJ Maxx
depends on the weather, you know?
I might. I don't know where my day will
go from here.
>> [laughter]
>> That's wild to me.
THAT'S
>> [laughter]
>> I'VE I'VE NEVER DREAMED OF THAT.
I remember the first night I was in
Denver I had a hard time falling asleep
cuz all I could think about is what if
my dog had diarrhea, you know?
[laughter]
I didn't see one person at that park
with a ladle. How do y'all pick this up?
>> [laughter]
>> IF I SEE YOU PICKING UP DOG DIARRHEA
WITH A BAG we're I'm going to go ahead
and call the cops. That's it.
And we're going to look at your internet
browser, Doug, cuz you're off the rails
out here.
That's diarrhea. That's a bag, my man.
It doesn't work.
>> [laughter]
>> I just don't know how we haven't come up
with a better way to pick it up yet.
I mean we're on hoverboards eating
powdered dinners and we're still
picking this stuff up with Smith's
grocery bags.
>> [laughter]
>> Y'all remember like in the third grade
when a little kid would throw up
macaroni and cheese in the hallway
and the janitor he'd come out of the
closet
and he'd pour this powder all
[clears throat] over that macaroni and
cheese and what was once liquid now
turns in and then now he just sweeps it
up. Now it's just powder. And then he'd
go right back into that closet.
WHERE IS THAT POWDER?
DO YOU KNOW HOW MUCH EASIER OUR LIFE YOU
GUYS DON'T HAVE TO PICK UP ANY MORE
WE'RE GOING TO DUST IT AND KICK IT.
IT'LL BE OVER. I'LL GO ON SHARK TANK.
I'LL DO IT LIVE. I'LL MAKE MARK CUBAN
LOOK ME IN THE EYES.
>> [laughter]
>> WE'RE GOING TO DUST IT AND KICK IT.
TIRED OF BENDING OVER. I MEAN, WITH A
bag I can see through that barely goes
over my hand, you know?
>> [laughter]
>> I don't know.
I wish I got worked up over things that
mattered, you know?
>> [laughter]
>> I'm just
I'm angry.
Moving out west, it's
This stuff I mean,
north Alabama
weather is something that is a big deal
to us.
Weather men are heroes.
Meteorologists are big deals. Out west,
mountain towns, I've learned quickly
that people
don't care about the 7-day forecast in
the mountains.
You guys have Patagonia jackets to turn
into golden retrievers to turn into
granola bars. I mean, they've got seven
zippers. You're going on a hike
regardless.
Where I'm from, if the weather man
misses the forecast, we might lose a
neighborhood, maybe an elementary
school.
>> [laughter]
>> It's a big deal.
>> Not out here.
You know? No It doesn't matter out here.
I'd like to be at the station when
they're just making the forecast.
Spinning a wheel, whatever it LANDS ON.
PARTLY CLOUDY. THEY ALL DRIVE SUBARUS.
NOBODY'S WATCHING.
>> [laughter]
>> I DON'T KNOW. THE WEATHER'S SUCH A BIG
DEAL WHERE I'm from. It's an
introduction to a lot of conversations.
I might be like, "Hey, my name's Derek.
It's hot out here. Nice to meet you."
Out west, I can't get people to talk to
me unless I'm holding a dog.
If you're not holding a dog, you're a
stranger.
Which is crazy. I go to the park, I'll
be walking my dog, some lady will come
up in yoga pants, ask him 14 questions,
and walk away, and not even glance at
me.
>> [laughter]
>> I end up saying SOMETHING LIKE, "MY
NAME'S DEREK, AND I LOVE CROCK-POTS!
>> [laughter]
>> AND IF YOU RUB MY BELLY, MY LEG SHAKES
LIKE HIS, TOO!"
>> [laughter]
>> WEATHER'S A BIG DEAL WHERE I'M FROM.
I DON'T KNOW. I was walking downtown
Denver the other day, it started to
rain, I pulled out an umbrella, people
looked at me like I was from the future.
Like I was a prophet or a wizard. This
lady, she walked up to me, she's like,
"My son's sick, will you kiss his head?
We've read all about you."
I was like, "I just saw the forecast.
So, I brought an umbrella. I'm growing
some squash."
>> [laughter]
[clears throat]
>> I don't know.
It's nice being out west, though.
There's things you learn, you know. I'd
never gone anywhere past Mississippi
until 5 years ago.
It's been quite the adventure.
Went through Kansas, which was one-time
deal for me in a car, you know. Flattest
place I've ever been in my entire life.
I've never been somewhere where I'm
from, it's kind of wild. We have turns
and trees, it's insane, you know?
There's curves.
>> [laughter]
>> You go to Kansas, and they're like,
"Where we're going is
that dot right out there.
And the closer we get, the bigger it'll
get."
But it did make me think that every
prison in the country should be in
Kansas.
Really, you could watch an inmate run
away all weekend.
>> [laughter]
>> IT JUST MAKES THE CONVERSATION IN THE
GUARD TOWER totally different, you know?
It's like, "Randy, don't shoot him.
I like to watch him give up."
>> [laughter]
>> Yeah, man, there's nothing They run away
for 3 days, and they can still read the
address on the prison, it breaks them.
>> [laughter]
>> Y'all are fun.
My favorite thing about living in the
big city though is taco trucks. I love
them.
And not just for I I think that it's a
fad that people love them. I have a real
Being from Harvest, Alabama, we don't
have TACO BUT WE HAVE WE HAVE TACO BELL,
WHICH IS A 15-MINUTE drive away. Some of
y'all get that. It's like a whole new
game of Oregon Trail.
You know, it's a tough trip, you know?
You don't want to take it around 11:00
p.m. I never dreamed that Taco Bell
would grow wheels and come to me.
I never saw that coming. And then this
taco truck that I saw
not too long ago had a flat tire and the
menu was written in crayon.
That's perfect. Where I'm from, down
south, the worse the venue, the better
the food. If you're ever driving through
Alabama and you see a porta-potty
billowing smoke, pull in and order the
full slab.
>> [laughter]
>> Get some potato salad. Have an afternoon
for yourself.
I walked up to the window on the left
side of the window was a big bottle of
green sauce.
It said, "For wimps."
On the other side, a big bottle of red
sauce written on that, "Not for wimps."
I'm just like y'all, I've never been
confronted by salsa before.
>> [laughter]
>> I was wearing some jeans that Brett
Favre does commercials for and will give
a little pushback, you know?
About that time a young lady came up,
she grabbed that tough guy sauce, poured
it all over her burrito. I was
immediately inspired.
I went over there and grabbed it, poured
it all over mine.
Went back to my apartment, it's about
11:00 p.m. at night. That's good taco
truck time.
And fourth meal is my favorite meal. I
love four I love eating dinner twice.
And I don't have to sell y'all on that,
I carry my work around.
>> [laughter]
>> BUT IT'S ALSO ONE OF THE MAIN REASONS I
LOVE IT IS IT'S THE ONLY only meal you
can take your pants off for.
And you don't have to believe me.
Tomorrow when you're making a bowl of
cereal, pull your jeans down. The family
will leave the kitchen.
>> [laughter]
>> BUT AROUND MIDNIGHT, TAKING YOUR PANTS
OFF IS JUST A DECLARATION that you're
done with that day. No more emails or
text messages. I'm in my underwear and a
t-shirt. We're going to heat up this
Chinese food and I'm going to call IT A
NIGHT.
>> [laughter]
>> I REMEMBER I GRABBED this burrito and
you want to when you eat fourth meal,
you want to get in front of the TV, you
know? Watch something fun, something
different. I like to watch Unsolved
Mysteries sometimes, you know, whole
family's dead, who did that? You know,
that's crazy. We got to go get them. You
know, they're out there still and y'all
got a movie or something?
BURRITOS FROM TACO TRUCKS ARE
INCREDIBLE. They look like toddlers with
aluminum foil wrapped around them.
Y'all know what I'm I mean big, big,
big.
I grabbed this thing. I took a bite out
of it and what happened to me has
happened everybody in this room.
My face caught on fire.
>> [laughter]
>> AND IT WASN'T LIKE, OH, I'VE GOT TOO
MUCH TEXAS PETE ON MY BAGEL BITES. IT
WAS LIKE, NO, THERE'S REAL FLAMES ON MY
FACE. I think my neighbor stays up late.
I could USE HIS HELP.
>> [laughter]
>> WE'VE ALL BEEN THERE. I GOT BUMPED IN
THE TURN. I WASN'T out of this race.
What do you need when something's too
spicy? Some milk, some dairy. You're at
a Mexican restaurant and the nachos are
spicy, you don't send them back. You go,
"Excuse me, ma'am. These nachos are
being a little bit of a pill. Could we
get one more sour cream?"
And then you smash it.
Okay. I know there's somebody in this
room that's like, "Must be nice to eat
as much dairy as you want, Derek."
>> [laughter]
>> WHERE ARE YOU?
YOU'RE PROBABLY THE SAME PERSON THAT
GETS 3 lbs of nachos and you put 1 lb of
sour cream on top and and that's what
made you poop in your hallway. I DON'T
BUY IT.
I'M SICK OF PEOPLE EATING ICE CREAM OUT
OF MIXING BOWLS AND THEY ARE SHOCKED
WHEN THEY HAVE TO [laughter] FART. I'M
OVER THAT.
I DON'T KNOW WHEN IT STARTED, LIKE 2009,
SOMEBODY WAS LIKE, [laughter] "DAIRY
MAKES MY TUMMY HURT." DAIRY, IT'S
SUPPOSED TO MAKE YOUR TUMMY HURT.
WHEN DOESN'T IT?
AND WE EAT DAIRY LIKE PSYCHOS IN THIS
COUNTRY. WE GET A GLASS, THE SAME GLASS
WE WATER OUR FERNS WITH, AND WE FILL IT
ALL THE WAY TO THE TOP, AND WE CHUG IT
AND GO, "OH MY GOODNESS, I MIGHT POOP."
>> [laughter]
>> IT MIGHT HAPPEN.
LET ME TELL YOU SOMETHING. IF YOU EAT A
BUNCH OF DAIRY, AND IN THE NEXT 3 days
you don't go to the bathroom and REALLY
IMPRESS YOURSELF, GO TO THE HOSPITAL.
>> [laughter]
[laughter]
>> I DID THIS BIT IN WISCONSIN, AND THEY
carried me into the streets.
>> [laughter]
>> All right.
Sorry about that.
>> [laughter]
>> I'm going to tell a joke here in a
minute.
And [laughter] I heard somebody say, "He
hasn't told one joke. He's just mad at
us. He's not."
I've been to these, and they tell jokes.
He He is mad at us. I've never
[laughter] met him. Have you met him?
I finished off that burrito.
So, I had some milk.
I wiped off the counters, hit the
lights,
went upstairs and made the mistake of
the night.
I scratched my backside.
>> [laughter]
>> Let me tell y'all something.
It's easy in this moment to be
judgmental, okay?
It's easy. It's easy. We're We're live,
you know?
But I want y'all to know something. Here
was the problem.
Here's where the problem lies. Where I'm
from, down south,
our hot sauce is vinegar-based, okay?
Frank's, Texas Pete, Louisiana, it's
just spicy vinegar.
And if it gets on your hands, it doesn't
matter.
It's just silly red water. That's so
silly. Look Look that.
That's so silly.
Out west, if you get a hold of a true
Hispanic hot sauce, it'll be pepper
based.
And if it gets in your sweat glands,
and you don't pressure wash it off,
>> [laughter]
>> it's still live.
So, when I touched my backside, I
started a brush fire immediately.
I mean, I felt the sting sting.
And I'm just as nervous AS Y'ALL. I
CAN'T TOUCH MY TOES. I NEED milk on my
butt, maybe. You know, I need something
crazy. [laughter] I THOUGHT ABOUT JUST
POURING IT IN THE FLOOR AND STOPPING IT
LIKE A BISCUIT. I'LL JUST SIT IN IT. I
need to sit in milk.
>> [laughter]
>> I panicked like anybody else would, you
know.
Freaked out.
Ran over to the freezer.
Grabbed an ice cube.
And at this point, it was it was a real
serious situation, you know. I mean, I
was hoo hoo ha.
One of those. It wasn't one of those
where I you know, I'm I'm going to fight
it off tonight. I needed an ice cube.
I remember I grabbed that ice cube, and
I was nervous about it.
For some reason, I thought about the
Christmas Story where the kid's tongue
gets stuck to the pole.
>> [laughter]
>> So, that made me nervous for some
reason.
So, I remember I I sucked on the ice
cube just a little bit.
And I squatted down with that thing. No,
you're going to watch me do this.
You don't know. We're going to put this
thing together. As soon AS THAT THING
TOUCHED ME, IT SOUNDED LIKE FAJITAS FROM
CHILI'S, my man.
Y'ALL ARE SO MUCH FUN. THANK y'all for
hanging [music] out.
>> [music]